$(document).ready(function () {
    
    var questions = [{
       question:"Which Friend hates thanksgiving?",
       answerList:["Ross","Chandler","Phoebe","Joey"],
       answer:1,
       image: "assets/images/thanksgiving.gif"
    },{
        question: "What Name did Ross say at the altar?",
        answerList: ["Emily","Nicole","Emma","Rachel"],
        answer:3,
        image:"assets/images/thanksgiving.gif"
    },{
        question:"What was the name of Chandler's on-again off-again girlfriend throughout the series?",
        answerList:["Julie","Susie","Mary-Angela","Janice"],
        answer:3,
        image:"assets/images/thanksgiving.gif"
    },{
        question:"Who officiated Monica and Chandlers Wedding?",
        answerList:["Phoebe", "Ross","Joey","A Greek Orthodox Priest"],
        answer:2,
        image:"assets/images/thanksgiving.gif"
    },{
        question:"What type of animal was Ross's pet by the name of Marcel?",
        answerList:["Dog","Cat","Monkey","Duck"],
        answer:2,
        image:"assets/images/thanksgiving.gif"
    },{
        question:"What is Phoebe's twin sisters name?",
        answerList:["Ursula","Regina","Jenny","Carol"],
        answer:0,
        image:"assets/images/thanksgiving.gif"
    },{
        question:"Which Friend was obese in high school?",
        answerList:["Joey","Monica","Rachel","Chandler"],
        answer:1,
        image:"assets/images/thanksgiving.gif"
    },{
        question:"What type of animals were Joey and Chandler's two pets?",
        answerList:["Dog & Cat","Chick & Duck","Monkey & Cat","Dog & Duck"],
        answer:1,
        image:"assets/images/thanksgiving.gif"
    },{
        question:"What' the name of Rachel and Monica's annoying neighbor?",
        answerList:["Mr. Heckles","Mr. Davis","Mr. Flanigan","Mr. Phalanges"],
        answer:0,
        image:"assets/images/thanksgiving.gif"
    },{
        question:"Who lives across the street from Monica & Rachel?",
        answerList:["Ugly Guy","Fat Guy","Ugly Naked Girl","Ugly Naked Guy"],
        answer:3,
        image:"assets/images/thanksgiving.gif"
    },{
        question:"How many times has Ross been married?",
        answerList:["5 times","3 times","7 times","4 times"],
        answer:1,
        image:"assets/images/thanksgiving.gif"
    },{
        question:"Who did Rachel leave at the altar?",
        answerList:["Ross","Barry","Paolo","Chandler"],
        answer:1,
        image:"assets/images/thanksgiving.gif"
    },{
        question:"Who does Monica marry?",
        answerList:["Joey","Richard","Chandler","Funny Bobby"],
        answer:2,
        image:"assets/images/thanksgiving.gif"
    },{
        question:"Who does Joey play on Days of our Lives",
        answerList:["Lucky Spencer","Dr. Drake Ramoray","Matt LeBlanc","Bo Brady"],
        answer:1,
        image:"assets/images/thanksgiving.gif"
    },{
        question:"Whats the name of Phoebe's altar ego",
        answerList:["princess consuela banana hammock","Frances","Regina Falange","Rachel Greene"],
        answer:2,
        image:"assets/images/thanksgiving.gif"
    },{
        question:"Who has a 'nubbin?",
        answerList:["Joey","Ugly Naked Guy","Richard","Chandler"],
        answer:3,
        image:"assets/images/thanksgiving.gif"
    },{
        question:"What is the name of Joey's Chair?",
        answerList:["Susie","Jenny","Rosita","Stevie"],
        answer:2,
        image:"assets/images/thanksgiving.gif"
    },{
        question:"When Ross was a kid whe created a comic book, What was the name of the main Character?",
        answerList:["DinoMan","Science Boy","Super Paleontologist","Bob"],
        answer:1,
        image:"assets/images/thanksgiving.gif"
    },{
        question:"Who always says, 'WE WERE ON A BREAK!'",
        answerList:["Chandler","Fun Bobby","Ross","The Mattress King"],
        answer:2,
        image:"assets/images/thanksgiving.gif"
    },{
        quetion:"What is Janice's famous catchphrase?",
        answerList:["Janice's day of fun!","OH.MY.GOD.","Mr. Chandler Bing","BingALing"],
        answer:1,
        image:"assets/images/thanksgiving.gif"
    }]
});